WSYR Collection
WSYR Collection
1930-1981
WSYR (Radio station: Syracuse, N.Y.)
14 linear ft.
Audiorecordings (78 and 33 RPM instantaneous discs and reel to reel tapes) and files from Syracuse radio station WSYR.
4526486
Biographical History
WSYR (570AM) is one of the oldest radio stations in the Syracuse, NY area. First broadcast on September 15, 1922 as WMAC in Cazenovia, NY, the station moved to Syracuse in 1928 and changed its call sign to WSYR. The station has long hosted local news and entertainment programming. For many years. it was the flagship station for broadcasts of Syracuse University football and men's basketball games.
The collection was donated by Alan Milair, a long-time broadcaster on WSYR. Best known for his 16-year stint as host of "Monster Movie Matinee," Mr. Milair served as a news anchor and weatherman, a talk show host, and as host of "Music Just For You" along with several classical music programs.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The WSYR Collection contains audiorecordings and files from the Syracuse, NY radio station.
Audiorecordings contains original recordings made either directly from NBC or Mutual radio feeds, or made for broadcast by WSYR, between 1939 and 1957. The collection largely consists of news broadcasts and speeches. The format is primarily 78 and 33 RPM instantaneous disc recordings, along with 176 reel to reel tapes. Many important events and public figures of the era are recorded on these broadcasts.
Files consists mostly of advertising logs (local and national), and detailed broadcast notes for more than forty years of programming. Also in this series are material relating to a dedicatory dinner for Syracuse University's Newhouse School honoring Samuel I. Newhouse, printed programs for WSYR's "Concert Hall" series, and assorted other items.
Other Formats Available
Approximately a third of the recordings, more than 400 items, has been digitized and is available in the WSYR Collection in.
Arrangement of the Collection
Audiorecordings are in chronological order, as they were received from the donor, but are listed alphabetically in the inventory below for ease of location of a particular title. Files are arranged alphabetically; original folder titles were retained, where present.
Subject and Genre Headings
New York State; Radio, television, film; Acheson, Dean, 1893-1971.; Aldrich, Henry R. (Henry Ray), 1891-; Arnold, Henry Harley, 1886-1950.; Arnold,Jackson D.; Attlee, C. R. (Clement Richard), 1883-1967.; Avila Camacho, Manuel, 1897-1955.; Baker, Bonnie.; Baker, Ernest Albert, 1869-; Barkley, Alben William, 1877-1956.; Bernthal, M.; Bernthal, Murray.; Borguionni,, Charles.; Bradley, Bill.; Brendler, Charles, 1898-1965.; Brinkley, David.; Brown, Glenn.; Brownell, Herbert, 1904-1996.; Burton, Howard, 1888-; Byrne, JP.; Carmichael, Stokely, 1941-1998.; Caruso, Guy.; Cassidy, Henry C. (Henry Clarence), 1910-1988; Cecil, Robert E.; Chamberlain, Neville, 1869-1940.; Chaplin, W. W. (William Watts), 1895-; Chiang, May-ling Soong, 1897-2003.; Chilton, Ruth.; Churchill, Winston, 1874-1965.; Clarke, Andy, -1948.; Clinton, Larry, 1909-1985.; Cole, Ned.; Cook, Joe.; Corcoran, Thomas.; Cramer, Lynn.; Cunningham, David.; Cuomo, Mario Matthew.; D'Amato, Alfonse.; Daladier, Edouard, 1884-1970.; Daver, Dan.; Daver, Don.; DeBernardis.; Delaski, Preston.; Denis, Elmer Conrad, 1920-; Dewey, Thomas E. (Thomas Edmund), 1902-1971.; Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870.; Diller, LeGrande A.; Doolittle, James Harold, 1896-1993.; Doubleday, Bob.; Dowdell, Dennis.; Dulles, John Foster, 1888-1959.; Eden, Anthony, Earl of Avon, 1897-1977.; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969.; Ekins, H. R. (Herbert Roslyn), 1901-; Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1926-; Everett, Bill.; Ford, Gerald R., 1913-2006.; Frederick, Pauline.; Frost, David, 1939-2013.; Frizell, Bernard.; Gallagher, Joe.; Gates, Chester.; Geiger, Ray.; George VI, King of Great Britain, 1895-1952.; Giraud, Henri, 1879-1949.; Goralski, Robert.; Göring, Hermann, 1893-1946.; Gray, John.; Harkness, Richard, 1907-1977.; Heur, ---.; Hillegar, Fred.; Hitler, Adolf, 1889-1945.; Hobart, Charles.; Hocut, Charlie.; Hoffman, Dick.; Holley, Adele, 1887-1970.; Hoover, J. Edgar (John Edgar), 1895-1972.; Hopkins, Harry L. (Harry Lloyd), 1890-1946.; Houston, Monty.; Hull, Cordell, 1871-1955.; Jeske, Fred.; Johnson, Bess.; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973.; Jones, Jack, 1884-1970.; Jordan, Max.; Keanse, Edward.; Kettering, Charles Franklin, 1876-1958.; Knauer, Virginia H.; Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.; La Guardia, Fiorello H. (Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947.; Lang Thompson Orchestra.; Leahy, William D.; Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963.; Levine, Irving R.; Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865.; Lindbergh, Charles A. (Charles Augustus), 1902-1974.; Lindsey, Jake William.; MacArthur, Douglas, 1880-1964.; MacVane, John.; Mariness, Joel.; Marshall, George C. (George Catlett), 1880-1959.; Mary, Queen, consort of George V, King of Great Britain, 1867-1953.; Massey, Raymond.; Milair, Alan.; Mink, Patsy T., 1927-2002.; Molotov, Vyacheslav Mikhaylovich, 1890-1986.; Morgan, Henry, 1915-1994.; Morris, Keith, 1919-1992.; Mueller, Merrill.; Murphy, Ed.; Mussolini, Benito, 1883-1945.; Newhouse, Samuel I.; Nimitz, Chester W. (Chester William), 1885-1966.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.; Osmeña, Sergio, 1878-1961.; Ottoway, Floyd.; Paley, William C.; Patrick, Keith.; Patton, George S. (George Smith), 1885-1945.; Pedder, Donald.; Pines, Philip A.; Purdy, Bill.; Ranking, Evelyn.; Reagan, Michael, 1945-; Reed, Kerid.; Rich, John, 1917-; Ridgway, Matthew B. (Matthew Bunker), 1895-1993.; Roberts, George.; Rogers, Roy, 1911-1998.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Rothbaum, Bill.; Russel, Kay.; Russel, Russ.; Santoro, Olivio.; Schultz, Bernice.; Shaw, Robert.; Smith, A. Merriman, 1913-1970.; Smith, Carleton, 1910-1984.; Smith, Malcolm.; Smuts, Jan Christiaan, 1870-1950.; Stalin, Joseph, 1878-1953.; Stapleton, Bernard.; Stettinius, Edward R., Jr. (Edward Reilly), 1900-1949.; Stevens, Bill.; Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1900-1965.; Stimson, Henry L. (Henry Lewis), 1867-1950.; Swing, Raymond, 1887-1968.; Thompson, Lang.; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.; Tucker, Orrin.; Tuckner, Howard.; Vadeboncoeur, E. R.; Wahl, Jim.; Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew, 1883-1953.; Wallace, Lurleen, 1926-1968.; Walters, Barbara, 1931-; Waring, Fred, 1900-1984.; Webb, Janet.; Wheaton, Charles.; Whitney, Fay.; Wicks, Arthur H., 1887-; Wilder, Harry C.; Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944.; Winant, John G. (John Gilbert), 1889-1947.; Witney, Bob.; Baltimore Orioles (American Association: Baseball team); Cleveland Orchestra.; Milwaukee Braves (Baseball team); New York Yankees (Baseball team); San Francisco Giants (Baseball team); Pittsburgh Pirates (Baseball team); WSYR (Radio station: Syracuse, N.Y.); News radio stations -- New York (State) -- Syracuse.; Radio broadcasting -- New York (State) -- Syracuse.; Radio broadcasting of sports.; Radio programs.; Syracuse (N.Y.); 78 rpm records.; Sound recordings.; Audiotapes.; Correspondence.; Logs (records); Long-playing records.; Photographs.; Press kits.; Programs (documents); Radio programs.
Access Restrictions
Access to recordings requires advance notice to produce a use copy.
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Alan Milair.
Inventory
- Audiorecordings
  Approximately a third of the recordings, more than 400 items, has been digitized and is available in the WSYR Collection in.
  - 1. Lyndon Johnson - Vietnam War; 2. Richard Nixon - Campaign Speech, 03/31/1968; 09/19/1968; wsyr_radio_973; includes order from George E. Davis, Manager Sales Traffic, NBC Radio Network to WSYR and other radio stations to broadcast Political program on behalf of the Nixon-Agnew Campaign committee; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 15:00 (Box 56)
    1. President Lyndon B. Johnson - Progress of Vietnam War, Speech with Surprise Announcement of his Not Being Available for 1968 Presidential Nomination; 2. Richard Nixon - Campaign Speech. Topic: What the President Should Mean
  - 1000 - C Beautiful Music, wsyr_radio_930; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 52)
  - 1936 World Series - New York Yankees vs. New York Giants - Game III - Tape 1 of 1, 10/03/1936; wsyr_radio_458; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - 1957 World Series - New York Yankees vs. Milwaukee Braves Game #7 - Tape II of III, 10/10/1957; wsyr_radio_459; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 36:39 (Box 11)
  - 1957 World Series - New York Yankees vs. Milwaukee Braves Game #7 - Tape III of III, 10/10/1957; wsyr_radio_460; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 52:41 (Box 11)
  - 1957 World Series Yankees vs. Milwaukee Game 6 (part 1 of 3), 10/09/1957; 12/14/1974; wsyr_radio_674; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 51:22 (Box 31)
  - 1957 World Series Yankees vs. Milwaukee Game 6 (part 2 of 3), 10/09/1957; wsyr_radio_675; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 54:12 (Box 31)
  - 1957 World Series Yankees vs. Milwaukee Game 6 (part 3 of 3), 10/09/1957; wsyr_radio_676; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 26:14 (Box 31)
  - 1957 World Series Yankees vs. Milwaukee Game 7 (part 1 of 3), 10/10/1957; wsyr_radio_677; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 70:47 (Box 31)
  - 1960 World Series Classics Pittsburgh Pirates vs. New York Yankees Game 7 (part 1 of 3), 10/13/1960; wsyr_radio_678; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 52:22 (Box 31)
  - 1960 World Series Classics Pittsburgh Pirates vs. New York Yankees Game 7 (part 2 of 3), 10/13/1960; wsyr_radio_679; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 56:35 (Box 31)
  - 1960 World Series Classics Pittsburgh Pirates vs. New York Yankees Game 7 (part 3 of 3), 10/13/1960; wsyr_radio_680; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 58:07 (Box 31)
  - 1962 World Series Yankees vs. Giants Game 5 (part 1 of 3), 10/10/1962; 07/31/1981; wsyr_radio_681; includes Budweiser Commercial; note on reel reads: "NBC recording on Ampex No. 2 only. For daily NBC recording only."; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 44:18 (Box 32)
  - 1962 World Series Yankees vs. Giants Game 5 (part 2 of 3); John Gray Show, Program 43, 10/10/1962; 05/21/1979; 07/29/1981; wsyr_radio_682; tape ends at end of 6th inning; additional information in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 53:38 (Box 32)
  - 1962 World Series Yankees vs. Giants Game 5 (part 3 of 3); WSYR AM on Air, 10/10/1962; 04/07/1978; 07/31/1981; wsyr_radio_683; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 57:15 (Box 32)
  - 1962 World Series Yankees vs. Giants Game 6 (part 1 of 3), 10/15/1962; 07/29/1981; 07/31/1981; wsyr_radio_684; tape ends after 4th inning; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 60:50 (Box 32)
  - 1962 World Series Yankees vs. Giants Game 6 (part 2 of 3), 10/15/1962; 07/31/1981; 08/01/1981; wsyr_radio_685; tape ends after 8th inning; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 57:52 (Box 32)
  - 1962 World Series Yankees vs. Giants Game 6 (part 3 of 3), 10/15/1962; 07/30/1981; 08/01/1981; wsyr_radio_686; tape ends with NBC chimes; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 9:23 (Box 32)
  - 1962 World Series Yankees vs. Giants Game 7 (part 1 of 3), 10/16/1962; 08/02/1981; wsyr_radio_687; tape ends at end of 3rd inning; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 52:35 (Box 32)
  - 1962 World Series Yankees vs. Giants Game 7 (part 2 of 3), 10/16/1962; 08/02/1981; wsyr_radio_688; tape ends at end of 7th inning; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 59:33 (Box 33)
  - 1962 World Series Yankees vs. Giants Game 7 (part 3 of 3), 10/16/1962; 08/02/1981; wsyr_radio_689; tape ends with NBC chimes; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 47:50 (Box 33)
  - 1965 World Series Dodgers vs. Twins Game 7 (part 1 of 3), 10/14/1965; 08/07/1981; wsyr_radio_690; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 57:00 (Box 33)
  - 1965 World Series Dodgers vs. Twins Game 7 (part 2 of 3), 10/14/1965; 08/07/1981; wsyr_radio_691; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 49:52 (Box 33)
  - 1965 World Series Dodgers vs. Twins Game 7 (part 3 of 3), 10/14/1965; 08/07/1981; 10/19 and 10/20 [no year]; wsyr_radio_692; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 47:06 (Box 33)
  - 1968 Presidential Election: Concession, Acceptance Statements by Nixon, Humphrey, Agnew., 11/06/1968; wsyr_radio_974; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 56)
  - 1971 World Series - Game 7 - Baltimore Orioles vs. Pittsburgh Pirates - Tape 2 of 3, 10/17/1971; wsyr_radio_469; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 50:20 (Box 13)
  - 1971 World Series Baltimore vs. Pittsburgh Game 7 (part 1 of 3), 10/17/1971; 02/26/1971; wsyr_radio_693; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 56:45 (Box 33)
  - 1971 World Series Baltimore vs. Pittsburgh Game 7 (part 3 of 3), 10/17/1971; wsyr_radio_694; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:00 (Box 33)
  - 1972 LeMoyne College Commencement - WSYR, wsyr_radio_493; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - 1972 Tip Off Achievement Awards Dinner, 03/17/1972; wsyr_radio_471; Bill Everett, Announcer; at Hotel Syracuse.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - 2000 - S Beautiful Music, wsyr_radio_931; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 53)
  - 4th Anniversary of the invasion of Poland by Hitler, part 1, fragment; B- Winston Churchill at Quebec/ the citadel, part 3 of 3, 08/31/1943; wsyr_radio_026; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 3)
  - 5 Star Generals - General [Jackson D.] Arnold (part 2), General [Douglas] MacAuther [sic]; Foreign Commisar [sic] Molotov (and translation), 05/08/1945; wsyr_radio_256; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - 5 Star Generals - General Marshall, General Eisenhower (parts 2 and 4); Mrs. Roosevelt, 05/08/1945; wsyr_radio_257; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - 5 Star Generals and Admirals: Admiral [William D.] Leahy (part 1 - Victory over Germany); 5 Star Generals - Admiral [Ernest] King, [Chester W.] Nimitz, General [Jackson D.] Arnold (part 3), 05/08/1945; wsyr_radio_252; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - A "Theatre Of The Mind" Production - "Love’s Savage Winds" - Episode 1, wsyr_radio_455; 1/2 inch audio tape; running time 17:42 (Box 11)
  - "A Christmas Carol" - Adaptation Of Dickens by Kerid Reed, 12/24/1971; wsyr_radio_490; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 27:45 (Box 15)
  - A Day in the Life of Chester Gates, 04/24/1978; wsyr_radio_549; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 19)
    (Open -- this will replace the TV open) On July first... one of the largest service organizations in Syracuse will mark a first... a first for the black community... and a first for the Syracuse Rotary. On that day... 63 year old Chester Gates will take over as president of the Syracuse Rotary... a post no black man has ever held. (Announcer) A Day In The Life Of Chester Gates... a presentation of WSYR Toatal News ... reported and produced by Jim Kenyon.
  - A Day in the Life of Dr. Melvin Beard, 07/16/1976; 07/25/1976; wsyr_radio_957; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 24:05 (Box 55)
  - A Tribute to Senator John Hughes (Percent grant from Onondaga), 10/14/1972; local news intro fragment; no opening and closing; Fred Hillegar, narrator; George S. Sullivan; T. Elmer Bean Bogardis; wsyr_radio_956; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:00 (Box 55)
  - A-Eisenhower Victory speech; Stevenson Concession speech, wsyr_radio_038; note on label reads: "Starts- I have Twice had that..., ends - Demons ..."; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 7)
    Eisenhower introduced by Vice President Nixon, Sheraton Park Hotel, Washington D. C.; Stevenson speech, Conrad Hilton Hotel, Grand Ballroom
  - Aaronson Auditorium, wsyr_radio_604; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Abraham Lincoln Program, 02/12/1974; wsyr_radio_918; note on label reads "To: Alan Milair -WSYR. O. C. C. - classes with credits- Richard A Cobb"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 9:15 (Box 52)
  - Acme Christmas Program; President Eisenhower - Talk to the Nation, 12/25/1953; 01/04/1954; wsyr_radio_416; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Adlai Stevenson at the Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, wsyr_radio_089; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 13)
  - Adlai Stevenson on Foreign Policy, 02/26/1953; wsyr_radio_099; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 15)
  - Adlai Stevenson speech, parts 1 and 2, 09/15/1953; wsyr_radio_070; at Chicago, Civic Opera House; closes with NBC Chimes; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 11)
  - Adolf Hitler (number 5 - ends of English translation); Adolf Hitler (number 5 - ends Hitler talking), 10/06/1939; wsyr_radio_129; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Adolf Hitler (number 6); BBC News, wsyr_radio_131; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Air Check of Civil Disorders on WSYR (part 3), 08/18 [no year]; wsyr_radio_1022; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 59)
  - Alan Milair Audition - announcing and use of his voice; Syracuse Community Health Center spots, wsyr_radio_632; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Alan Milair Birthday, 03/01/1969; wsyr_radio_484; Made at WSYR: Floyd O’Howay, Myron Levy, Carl Silfer.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Alan Milair Show - daytime with commercials and closing theme, 07/01/1966; wsyr_radio_480; Bill Everett does an I.D. Partial Show.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Allied Generals - Patton (part 3); Harry Hopkins, 05/08/1945; wsyr_radio_258; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Always, song by Bill Stevens, wsyr_radio_435; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - American forum of Air - Communism in churches (parts 1 and 2), wsyr_radio_365; Lacquer discs/acetates
    1947, American forum of the air, NBC program. YWCA commercial, Frank Blair - mediator. Side 1 ends with: "pertainant", side 2 starts with "overlap". Speakers - Bishop Garfield Bromley Oxnam, Rev. Donald Jackson. Ends with next week program
  - Americans with handicaps, wsyr_radio_625; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 2:15 (Box 25)
    1 & 2 - Control data Corp.; 3 & 4 - United Engineers; 5 & 6 - East Wind Group
  - Arrival - Vadeboncoeur and Wheaton; [second side unknown], 07/12/1946; wsyr_radio_321; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Arrival of Corporal Hickox at Hancock airport; [unknown], 05/13/1953; wsyr_radio_410; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Audio of TV Ladies Day morning show, following Kay Russell’s death, wsyr_radio_914; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 51)
  - Audition, Alan Milair, part 1, wsyr_radio_081; B - UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 17)
  - Australian Almanac - WSYR, wsyr_radio_563; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Australian Almanac 17, Jul 1981; wsyr_radio_927; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:00 (Box 52)
    "This program is sent to you through the courtesy of the Australian Information Service. It is compiled and edited by Terry Hughes, an Australian broadcaster." 1 - Dudley Carter, World Champion Gum Leaf player, gives an example of his unusual talent on location in the local pub; 2 - Interview with Thomas Kinneally, one of Australia’s foremost novelists, and author of Confederates, a novel about the American Civil War; set in Virginia in 1862, it has received wide acclaim; 3 - Iris Anderson is a blush nurse for many of the orphaned and injured animals which inhabit Australia’s bush; 4 - John Hutchinson is and Australian bird call collector with some of the most unique and best recorded bird calls in existence
  - Barbara Walters interview with Mrs. George Wallace, 06/02/1972; wsyr_radio_494; used w/ "WSYR Womens’ World"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Baseball game fragments - Yankees vs. Brewers, wsyr_radio_605; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Ben Schwartzwalder Talks Football, 09/09/1971; 09/12/1971; wsyr_radio_964; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 55)
  - [Benito] Mussolini - "Italian declaration of war"; NBC News Roundup (part 2), 06/09/1940; 06/10/1940; wsyr_radio_137; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Bernard "Bud" Stapleton - Vadeboncoeur; Keepsake (3B), 10/02/1945; 1945; wsyr_radio_284; Lacquer discs/acetates
    A - WSYR program: Stapleton - Tokyo story and homecoming. He was also an announcer ate WSYR. First flag raising on Tokyo, first landing by air in Japan, first entry into Tokyo. B - "Keepsake Time" - 2 cuts: 1 - song "If I love you" from Carousel; 2 - song "All of my life". Keepsake diamond rings".
  - Bicentennial Facts and Legends, Hosted by John Warner Episodes 1 thru 5, wsyr_radio_1003; Warner was Administrator of the American Revolution Bicentennial Administration; box 1 of 6; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 58)
  - Bicentennial Facts and Legends, Hosted by John Warner Episodes 1 thru 5, 02/14/1976; 02/15/1976; 02/22/1976; wsyr_radio_1004; Warner was Administrator of the American Revolution Bicentennial Administration; box 2 of 6; note on the label reads "Cuts: 1, 2, 3 used 02/14-15/1976; 4, 5 use 02/22/1976"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 58)
  - Bicentennial Facts and Legends, Hosted by John Warner Episodes 11 thru 14, wsyr_radio_1005; Warner was Administrator of the American Revolution Bicentennial Administration; box 3 of 6; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 19:45 (Box 58)
    11: John Adams (5:00); 12: The Events of Independence (5:00); 13: George Washington (5:00); 14: Blacks and The Bicentennial (4:45)
  - Bicentennial Facts and Legends, Hosted by John Warner Episodes 15 thru 18, wsyr_radio_1006; Warner was Administrator of the American Revolution Bicentennial Administration; box 4 of 6; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 19:45 (Box 58)
    15: Deborah Sampson (5:00); 16: John Honeyman (5:00); 17: Medicine and the Revolution (4:45); 18: Unsung Heroes (5:00)
  - Bicentennial Facts and Legends, Hosted by John Warner Episodes 19 thru 22, wsyr_radio_1007; Warner was Administrator of the American Revolution Bicentennial Administration; box 5 of 6; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 20:00 (Box 58)
    19: Patriotic Songs (5:00); 20: Haym Solomon (5:00); 21: The Bicentennial (5:00); 22: John Marshall (5:00)
  - Bicentennial Facts and Legends, Hosted by John Warner Episodes 27 thru 30, 06/26/1976; wsyr_radio_1008; Warner was Administrator of the American Revolution Bicentennial Administration; box 6 of 6; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 20:00 (Box 58)
    27: Boston Tea Party, 06/26/1976 (5:00); 28: Inventions (5:00); 29: Statue of Liberty, 06/26/1976,(5:00); 30: Andrew Carnegie (5:00)
  - Bill Rothrum[?] at "The Dentist" (part 2), wsyr_radio_436; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Bishop Hines Sermon on the Diocese’s Sesquicentennial, wsyr_radio_596; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Black College Choirs, 02/16/1977; 02/20/1977; wsyr_radio_713; includes scripts; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 54:20 (Box 36)
    Special program on behalf of the United Negro College Fund: Wednesday 2/16/77; 8:05-9 PM; (repeat) Sunday 2/20/77; 5:05-3 PM. United Negro College Fund is a non-profit organization that conducts fundraising campaigns in order to raise money for operating expenses of 41 predominantly black colleges and universities.
  - Blossom Music Festival, Cleveland Orchestra, radio spots, wsyr_radio_626; two radio spot advertisements; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Bockman (30 seconds spot), wsyr_radio_1002; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 0:30 (Box 58)
  - Bonneville Broadcasting: Sounds of Sinatra, promos and logos, wsyr_radio_606; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Bonneville Program Services: Adult Programming: Program I and II, wsyr_radio_933; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 53)
  - Bresee Chevrolet spots with music beds for voiceovers, wsyr_radio_607; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Buy George Campaign, 10/27/1975; wsyr_radio_1024; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 59)
  - Campaign for Human Development PSA’s, Bishop David Cunningham, Diocese of Syracuse, wsyr_radio_627; 3 cuts, Sunday, Nov. 19 donation, Alan Milair, announcer; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Captain John Swift interview; [illegible], 01/06/1952; wsyr_radio_391; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Chamberlain resignation, 05/10/1940; wsyr_radio_122; Lacquer discs/acetates